Guide to the Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection - Addition
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Adele Gutman Nathan theatrical collection: addition
1901-1986
YCAL MSS 82
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
9.5
(17 boxes)
The Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection Addition consists of letters, manuscripts, printed material, and photographs documenting Nathan's life and achievements in the theater, as an author, as a journalist, and as a pageant producer. Included are drafts of children's books about the lives of Winston Churchill and Abraham Lincoln, programs for the Cellar Players and the Little Lyric Theatre, production notes for a centennial celebration for Rochester, New York, and radio scripts. Materials in this collection also document the history of the Gutman family, Jewish merchants in Baltimore during the turn of the 20th century. Included are materials documenting the life of Nathan's sister, Elizabeth Gutman Kaye, a painter and singer of folk songs.
Nathan, Adele Gutman
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Bequeathed to the Beinecke Library by Adele Gutman Nathan in 1986. For further information, see the Description of the Collection, below.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Restricted Fragile Papers in box 17 may only be consulted with permission of the appropriate curator. Preservation photocopies for reference use have been substituted in the main files.
Associated Materials
Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection. YCAL MSS 58
ADELE GUTMAN NATHAN (1889-1986) and ELIZABETH GUTMAN KAYE (1891-1971)
Biographical sketches of Adele Gutman Nathan and Elizabeth Gutman Kaye are provided in the register for YCAL MSS 58, the Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection.
Scope and Contents
The Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection - Addition forms an adjuct part of the previously processed Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection (YCAL MSS 58). This group of material consists of manuscripts, working notes, letters, photographs, printed materials, and scripts which document the life and works of Adele Nathan as well as her sister, Elizabeth Gutman Kaye. The papers span the years 1901-1986. The materials in this register were bequeathed to the Beinecke Library in accordance with terms of Nathan's will following her death in 1986, but were sent instead to the Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Museum in Baltimore, Maryland. After the original group of papers were processed, the Beinecke Library forwarded several boxes of railroadiana to the B&O Museum (in accordance with Nathan's will) and subsequently received from the B&O Museum the supplementary material listed herein.
The collection is housed in 17 boxes and consists of six series: Writings, Projects, Correspondence, Personal Papers, Photographs, and Elizabeth Gutman Kaye Papers. Boxes 13-16 contain Oversize material. Box 17 contains Restricted Fragile Papers. The arrangement of series in this register duplicates that of the original Adele Gutman Nathan Theatrical Collection (YCAL MSS 58).
Of note among the materials in Series I, Writings, are items in the Books subseries: extensive drafts of Churchill's England, How to Plan and Conduct a Bicentennial Celebration and Lincoln's America, the latter including proof paste-ups. A number of printed columns written by Nathan during the 1920s are found in the Columns subseries. Among the Pageants materials are drafts of production and promotional items for Gettysburg Centennial (including a motion picture of the preceedings) and Niagarama.
Series II, Projects, Series III, Correspondence, Series IV, Personal Papers (Boxes 18-22), and Series V, Photographs, (all in box 9) contain a few ephemeral and written items which supplement the original collection. The contents of the two scrapbooks in Series IV are as follows: Scrapbook: "Four Industrial Pageants" contains material about: the Weirton Steel Company Labor Day pageants; the Columbia University Bicentennial; Paradise Hills; and Railroads on Parade (from the 1939 New York Worlds Fair). Scrapbook: [Nathan-Lanin Productions] contains material about: the Gettysburg Centennial; The Farmer Sows His Wheat; Youth United; the Columbia University Bicentennial; the Weirton Steel Company Labor Day pageants, the Lions International Convention's "Carolina Jamboree"; a concert of George Gershwin music; a milk industry convention; and a performance by the Royal Danish Ballet.
Series VI, Elizabeth Gutman Kaye Papers (Boxes 25-26), contains materials relating to the life of Adele Nathan's sister, who was a concert singer and a watercolor artist.
Boxes 13-16 contain Oversize material.
Children's literature, American -- History and criticism; Community theater; Jews -- Maryland -- Maryland -- Baltimore -- History; Jews -- United States -- Centennial celebrations, etc.; Little theater movement; Pageants -- United States -- History -- 20th Century; Radio authorship; Theater -- Production and direction; Young adult literature -- History and criticism; Baltimore (Md.) -- History; Rochester (N.Y.) -- Centennial celebrations, etc.; Folk singers; Journalists -- United States; Theatrical producers and directors; Woman authors; Churchill, Winston, 1874-1965 -- Juvenile literature -- History and criticism; Kaye, Elizabeth Gutman, 1891-1971; Lincoln, Abraham, 1809-1865 -- Juvenile literature -- History and criticism; Nathan, Adele Gutman; Cellar Players (New York, N. Y.); Goucher College; Joel Gutman & Co. (Baltimore, Md.); Little Lyric Theatre (Baltimore, Md.); Weirton Steel Co. (Weirton, W. Va.); Gutmann family
- Writings, 1901-86; Series I; 3.5; (9 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  Series I, Writings, is subdivided into seven alphabetically arranged subseries: Books, Proposed Book Projects, Columns, Pageants, Radio Scripts, Shorter Works, and Research Materials.
  - BOOKS
    - Churchill's England
      - Outlines, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Background clippings, 1962-69 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
      - Background notes (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Introduction - drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Draft 1 (partial), typescript, corrected, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Draft 1, typescript carbon, corrected, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 7-9)
      - Draft 2, typescript and carbon, corrected (Box 1, Folder 10)
      - Draft 2, typescript carbon, corrected, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
      - Draft 3, typescript carbon, corrected, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
      - Setting typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
      - Correspondence, 1962 Oct (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Announcements and reviews, 1963-66 (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Draft pages [for memorial edition?], typescript and carbon, corrected, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Illustration by Earl Mayer in art school brochure, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - The Farmer Sows His Wheat
      - Draft pages, typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Galley pages, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 23)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Review, 1932 Oct 22 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - How to Plan and Conduct a Bicentennial Celebration
      - Research material, 1969-74 (Box 2, Folder 27-30)
        (including discarded draft pages)
      - Drafts, 1969, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 31-34)
      - Drafts, 1969, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 34a-34b)
      - Setting typescripts, 1971, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 34c-34d)
      - Banner illustration depicting parade participants
        Related Archival Materials note
        See: Oversize, Box 13, folder 198
      - Illustrations (Box 3, Folder 3.4E-33)
        See also: Oversize, Box 14, folder 199
      - Publicity material, 1969-73 (Box 3, Folder 34g-34h)
      - Correspondence, 1964-79 (Box 4, Folder 35-36a)
      - Related article for Retirement Living, draft, typescript, and printed versions, 1975, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - The Iron Horse
      - Announcement, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Lincoln's America
      - Research material, 1957-80 (Box 4, Folder 39-42)
        [Includes general information on Civil War subjects]
      - Research notes, 1957-62 (Box 4, Folder 43)
      - "1960 Notes #1", typescript carbon, corrected (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - "1960 Notes #2", typescript carbon, corrected, 1960 May (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - "1960 Notes #3", typescript carbon, corrected (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - "1961 Notes", typescript carbon, corrected (Box 5, Folder 47)
      - "Original text" [discarded draft pages], typescript and carbon, corrected, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 48)
      - "Final Script", typescript carbon, 1961 Mar (Box 5, Folder 49)
      - "Re-write by Thorne", typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 50)
      - "Galley proof notes", 1959-61 (Box 5, Folder 51)
      - Galley corrections, 1960 Mar 30 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      - Second proof paste-ups, [1961] (Box 5, Folder 53-53c)
      - Set of unbound pages, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 54)
      - Book jacket, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 55)
      - Announcement and advertisements, 1961, 1986, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 56)
      - Correspondence, 1960-63 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Major John André
      - Advertisement, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - What is a Man Profited?
      - Draft pages, typescript, corrected, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - PROPOSED BOOK PROJECTS
    - The Age of Steam
      - Outline, draft pages, typescript, 1958, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Earth Shrinkers
      - Notes, 1964, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Isembard Kingdom Brunel
      - Outline, typescript and carbon (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - George Stephenson and the Rocket
      - Correspondence with notes, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 63)
      - Sample chapter drafts with outlines, typescript and carbon, corrected, 1954-58 (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - He Was Impeached
      - [Background?] clipping, 1974 Jun 30 (Box 6, Folder 65)
      - Outlines drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 66)
      - Sample chapter pages, typescript and carbon, corrected, 1973-74 (Box 6, Folder 67)
      - Correspondence with notes, 1973-74 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - A Mechanical History of the United States
      - Proposal, typescript and carbon (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - The Numerical Telegraph
      - Proposal with letter, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Smoke Signals to Satellites
      - Proposal notes with correspondence, 1964, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Background printed material and clippings for book ideas, 1950-63, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 72)
  - COLUMNS
    - "The Arts," Baltimore Daily Post
      - Printed columns, 1923-24 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - "Post Impressions," Baltimore Daily Post
      - Printed columns, 1924-26 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - [Various articles on the arts]
      From Baltimore Daily Post and The New York Telegram
      - Printed columns (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - [Untitled columns on radio programs] (Box 6, Folder 76)
      From The New York Telegram
  - PAGEANTS
    - George Washington Bicentennial
      - Notes and clippings, [ca. 1932] (Box 6, Folder 77)
      - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Gettysburg Centennial
      - Drafts of program with notes, typescript and carbon, [1963 (Box 6, Folder 79)
      - Printed programs, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 80)
      - Clippings, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 81-82)
      - Printed material, 1963, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 83)
      - Stationery and banner (Box 6, Folder 84)
      - Photographs, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 85)
      - Motion picture film of events, [1963] (Box 6, Folder 86)
      - Sound recording [on film stock] of Pickett's Charge reenactment, [1963] (Box 6, Folder 87)
      - Correspondence, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 88)
      - Invitations to Gettysburg-related events, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 89)
    - Mr. Lincoln Goes to Gettysburg
      - Master script, 1952 Sep 27 (Box 7, Folder 90)
      - Film adaptation for "News Magazine of the Screen"
        - Press release, 1952 Nov 6 (Box 7, Folder 91)
        - Photographs, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 92)
      - Play adaptation, outline, typescript carbon, 1962 Jun 14 (Box 7, Folder 93)
    - Niagarama
      - Background research material, 1951-62 (Box 7, Folder 94-96)
      - Notes, 1961, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 97)
      - Library call slips, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 98)
      - Text drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected, 1960-61, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 99-105)
        [Written with Lester Polakov]
      - Blueprints for floor layout, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 106)
      - [Drafts for labels?], 1961 (Box 7, Folder 107)
      - Outline for a guide book, draft, typescript and carbon (Box 7, Folder 108)
      - Pamphlet, drafts, typescript and carbon, corrected with printed copies (Box 7, Folder 109)
      - Press releases, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 110)
      - Correspondence, 1960-61 (Box 7, Folder 111)
      - Photographs, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 112)
      - Clippings, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 113)
      - Post-project information on Niagara Falls, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 114)
      - Related article - "Let's go to Niagara Falls," drafts, typescript and carbon, 1964 Jul 30 (Box 7, Folder 115)
    - Paradise Hills
      - Photograph, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 116)
    - Rochester Pageant of Progress
      - Director's script, 1934 (Box 7, Folder 117)
      - Costume designs, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 118-118a)
      - Stationery, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 119)
    - Weirton Steel Company
      1941 Labor Day Celebration
      - "These Our Freedoms" [play], master script, 1941
        See: Oversize, Box 14, folder 200
  - RADIO SCRIPTS
    - These Make America
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 120)
        [Incorporating Hans Christian Andersen's "The Fir Tree"]
  - SHORTER WORKS
    - "Batya," typescript, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 121)
    - The Children's Monthly Review, printed pages, 1901 (Box 8, Folder 122)
    - "The Cone Collection of Baltimore," printed version Vogue magazine, 1950 Mar 1 (Box 8, Folder 123)
    - "The Dangers of Travel," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 124)
    - [Gettyburg eyewitness article for Newsbreak ]
      - Drafts, typescript and carbon (Box 8, Folder 125)
      - Publicity photographs, 1970, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 126)
    - "Less Noise There," typescript, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 127)
    - "Lincoln's Unknown Gettysburg Address," printed version, This Week, 1966 Nov 13
      See: Oversize, Box 14, folder 201
    - "Love Song: Spring Thoughts" [Music by Louis H. Fisher], n.d.
      See: Oversize, Box 14, folder 202
    - "A Mencken Momento," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 128)
    - "Springboards to Success," typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 129)
    - "Street Scene: 1928," New York Times Magazine, printed pages, 1947 Feb 2 (Box 8, Folder 130)
    - "Ten Pillars of Poise," typescript, 1938 Sep 6 (Box 8, Folder 131)
    - "U.S. Overseas 'Cultural Offensive' Needs Publicity Help" [article written with David Safer], printed version, Overseas Press Bulletin with reprint from Congressional Report, 1957 Dec 28 (Box 8, Folder 132)
    - "When Big Business Celebrates," typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 133)
    - Miscellaneous pages and notes, 1955, 1959, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 134)
  - RESEARCH MATERIALS
    - "Historical reference" printed items concerning the Civil War, Abraham Lincoln, U.S. Bicentennial and other subjects, ca. 1950-75 (Box 9, Folder 135-141)
      See also: Oversize, box 14, folder 203
- Projects, 1920-54; Series II; 0.1; (.25 box)
  - Cellar Players
    - Programs, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 142)
  - Columbia University Bicentennial
    - Program, [1954] (Box 10, Folder 143)
    - Photograph, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 144)
  - Everybody's Playhouse
    - Programs, 1920-21 (Box 10, Folder 145)
  - Little Lyric Theatre
    - Set illustrations, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 146)
    - Programs, 1920-23 (Box 10, Folder 147)
- Correspondence, 1914-74; Series III; 0.1; (.25 box)
  - "A"-"D" general, 1914-70 (Box 10, Folder 148)
    Includes: Milton Baker, Blevins Davis, Anita Diamant, Owen Dodson
  - Brown University, 1975
    See: Oversize, Box 14, folder 204
  - "E"-"H" general, 1941-74, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 149)
    Includes: Dwight D. Eisenhower, Edward Finney
  - "J"-"O" general (Box 10, Folder 150)
    Includes: Elizabeth Kaye
  - "P"-"W" general, 1932-69 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Unidentified, 1972, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - Fan letters from children, 1959-72 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Blank postcards, 1950, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 154)
- Personal Papers, 1919-63; Series IV; 0.1; (.25 box)
  - Bowling song sheet, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 155)
  - Caricature of a man, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 156)
  - Certificate from American Theatre Wing Service, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Clippings
    - Baltimore Sun re: suffragists, Wilson Terrace, and AGN's career, 1915 May 2 (Box 10, Folder 158)
    - General (including ideas for writings), 1834-1983 (Box 10, Folder 159)
    - AGN and Works by AGN, 1920-63, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 160)
  - Identification cards, 1930-50 (Box 10, Folder 161)
  - Menus, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 162)
  - Pamphlet - proposal for memorial to John Oldmixon Lambdin, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 163)
  - Personal notes, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 164)
  - Poster for "A Thousand Years Ago" [directed by AGN], [1919?] (Box 10, Folder 165)
  - Print: Julia Ward Howe, n.d.
    See: Oversize, Box 14, folder 205
  - Print: "North West View of Buffalo, N.Y.", n.d.
    See: Oversize, Box 14, folder 206
  - Printed illustration [of Baltimore?], n.d. (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - Product advertisements, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 167)
  - Report to Overseas Press Club [transcript in Spanish], n.d. (Box 10, Folder 168)
    [Includes notes on last page]
  - Scrapbook: "Four Industrial Pageants", ca. 1939-61
    See: Oversize, Box 14, folders 207-211
  - Scrapbook: [Nathan-Lanin Productions], ca. 1925-55
    See: Oversize, Box 15, folders 212-214
  - Winston Churchill calendar, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 169)
- Photographs, ca. 1920-33; Series V; 0.1; (.25 box)
  - Museum of the City of New York: communications exhibit, [1933] (Box 10, Folder 170)
  - [Overseas Press Club?], n.d.
    See: Oversize, Box 14, folder 215
  - Theatrical productions, ca. 1920s (Box 10, Folder 171)
    [Includes Cellar Players]
  - Miscellaneous subjects, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 172)
    [Includes: AGN in Sweden, AGN with Lyndon B.Johnson, AGN receiving award for Lincoln's America, Cardinal Gasparri, and [Fannie Hurst?]
- Elizabeth Gutman Kaye Papers, 1910-72; Series VI; 1; (2 boxes)
  - CORRESPONDENCE
    - General, 1924-65 (Box 11, Folder 173)
      Includes: "Willi," Dorothy Nevile Lees, --- Giannini and Unidentified
  - EXHIBITIONS
    - List of paintings, 1966 Dec 23 (Box 11, Folder 174)
    - Publicity and reviews, 1947-67 (Box 11, Folder 175)
    - Programs and posters, 1945-69 (Box 11, Folder 176)
  - GRAPHIC WORKS
    - "Wall Fountain-Sabará", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - "Turkey-Woman", 1936 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - "Carnations for sale at Xochimilco", 1936 (Box 11, Folder 117)
    - "Street Scene-Taxco", 1936 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - "Waiting for tht Confessional-Mexico City", 1936 (Box 11, Folder 177)
    - Sketchbook, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 178)
  - PERSONAL PAPERS
    - Obituaries, 1971 Apr (Box 11, Folder 179)
    - Permission to paint in Palermo, Sicily, 1950 Mar 31 (Box 11, Folder 180)
    - Scrapbook of trip to Brazil, 1948 (Box 11, Folder 181-187)
      Includes letters from Herschel V. Johnson
    - Ship passenger lists with souvenir booklet, 1950 (Box 11, Folder 188)
  - PERFORMANCES
    - Program, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 189)
    - Recordings (3 sound reels)
      See: Oversize, box 16, folder 216-218
  - PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Exhibitions, 1964, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 190)
    - Memorial exhibitions, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 191)
    - Paintings, 1957, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 192)
    - Portraits of Elizabeth Kaye, 1910, 1921, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 193)
    - Snapshots and group shots, 1952, 1954, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 194)
  - WRITINGS
    - Patches of Light
      - Announcements, 1962, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 195)
    - Poems, typescript, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 196)
      With letter to Nannine Joseph
  - PROGRAMS
    - Collection of theater, opera, exhibition and performance programs, ca. 1930-54 (Box 12, Folder 197)
- Oversize, 1925-75; 4; (4 boxes)
  - WRITINGS
    - Books
      How to Plan and Conduct a Bicentennial Celebration
      - Banner illustration depicting parade participants (Box 13, Folder 198)
      - Illustrations, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 199)
    - Pageants
      Weirton Steel Company
      - 1941 Labor Day Celebration - "These Our Freedoms" [play], master script (Box 14, Folder 200)
    - Shorter Works
      - "Lincoln's Unknown Gettysburg Address," printed version, This Week, 1966 Nov 13 (Box 14, Folder 201)
      - "Love Song: Spring Thoughts", n.d. (Box 14, Folder 202)
      - [Music by Louis H. Fisher]
    - Research Materials
      - "Historical reference" printed items concerning the Civil War, Abraham Lincoln, U.S. Bicentennial and other subjects, ca. 1950-75 (Box 14, Folder 203)
  - CORRESPONDENCE
    - Brown University, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 204)
  - PERSONAL PAPERS
    - Print: Julia Ward Howe, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 205)
    - Print: "North West View of Buffalo, N.Y.", n.d. (Box 14, Folder 206)
    - Scrapbook: "Four Industrial Pageants", ca. 1939-61 (Box 14, Folder 207-211)
    - Scrapbook: [Nathan-Lanin Productions], ca. 1925-55 (Box 15, Folder 212-214)
  - PHOTOGRAPHS
    - [Overseas Press Club?], n.d. (Box 14, Folder 215)
  - ELIZABETH GUTMAN KAYE PAPERS
    - Performances
      - Recordings (3 sound reels) (Box 16, Folder 216-218)
- Restricted Fragile Papers, 0.5; (1 box)
  Box 17 contains fragile originals. The material is arranged in folder order and may only be seen with the permission of the appropriate curator.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 11 (Box 17, Folder 219)
  - Box 1, folder 12 (Box 17, Folder 220)
  - Box 1, folder 13 (Box 17, Folder 221)
  - Box 2, folder 22 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Box 2, folder 23 (Box 17, Folder 223)
  - Box 2, folder 26 (Box 17, Folder 224)
  - Box 5, folder 48 (Box 17, Folder 225)
  - Box 5, folder 59 (Box 17, Folder 226)
  - Box 6, folder 64 (Box 17, Folder 227)
  - Box 6, folder 73 (Box 17, Folder 228)
  - Box 6, folder 74 (Box 17, Folder 229)
  - Box 6, folder 75 (Box 17, Folder 230)
  - Box 6, folder 77 (Box 17, Folder 231)
  - Box 5, folder 60 (Box 17, Folder 232)
  - Box 6, folder 67 (Box 17, Folder 233)
  - Box 6, folder 86 (Box cs, Folder 233a)
  - Box 6, folder 87 (Box cs, Folder 233b)
  - Box 7, folder 93 (Box 17, Folder 234)
  - Box 8, folder 133 (Box 17, Folder 235)
  - Box 8, folder 134 (Box 17, Folder 236)
  - Box 10, folder 153 (Box 17, Folder 237)
  - Box 10, folder 157 (Box 17, Folder 238)
  - Box 7, folder 111 (Box 17, Folder 239)
  - Box 7, folder 100 (Box 17, Folder 240)
  - Box 10, folder 160 (Box 17, Folder 241)
  - Box 10, folder 166 (Box 17, Folder 242)